<resources>
    <string name="app_name">LockedUntil</string>
    <string name="store_title">🔒 Save</string>
    <string name="hint_secret">Secret text</string>
    <string name="hint_email">Email</string>
    <string name="hint_master">Master password</string>
    <string name="hint_view">View password</string>
    <string name="hint_date">Unlock date (YYYY-MM-DD)</string>
    <string name="store_button">Store</string>
    <string name="store_desc">On this page you create a new record; optionally specify an access date to time-lock the data.</string>
    <string name="hint_title">Title</string>
    <string name="retrieve_title">🔓 Retrieve</string>
    <string name="retrieve_desc">On this page you retrieve previously stored data with ID and password. If a time lock is set, the content is not shown before the access day.</string>
    <string name="hint_id">ID</string>
    <string name="hint_password">Password</string>
    <string name="retrieve_button">Retrieve</string>
    <string name="use_cases_button">📚 Use Cases</string>
    <string name="why_trust_button">🛡️ Why Trust</string>
    <string name="home_button">Home</string>
    <string name="toggle_language">Switch Language</string>
    <string name="use_cases_title">Use Cases</string>
    <string name="use_cases_investment_title">Investment Discipline</string>
    <string name="use_cases_investment_desc">Lock your own instructions to the future to limit emotional decisions and prevent panic selling.</string>
    <string name="use_cases_investment_sample">Sample Flow: An investment plan is saved and the unlock date set after a volatile period.</string>
    <string name="use_cases_investment_ethics">Ethical Note: Content is not financial advice; financial decisions are your responsibility.</string>
    <string name="use_cases_will_title">Will / Last Wish</string>
    <string name="use_cases_will_desc">Securely stores instructions or messages that must be executed after death.</string>
    <string name="use_cases_will_sample">Sample Flow: The user saves the will text, sets an unlock date and leaves credentials with a legal representative.</string>
    <string name="use_cases_will_ethics">Ethical Note: The platform is not a substitute for a legal will; official procedures should be followed.</string>
    <string name="use_cases_emergency_title">Emergency Sharing</string>
    <string name="use_cases_emergency_desc">Securely delivers passwords or critical data to relatives if something happens to the individual.</string>
    <string name="use_cases_emergency_sample">Sample Flow: The user saves an emergency note, and stores the ID and password with a trusted person.</string>
    <string name="use_cases_emergency_ethics">Ethical Note: Information should only be shared with trusted parties; responsibility lies with the user.</string>
    <string name="use_cases_threat_title">Threat / Exposure Scenario</string>
    <string name="use_cases_threat_desc">Data you want revealed if you are harmed remains locked until the defined conditions are met.</string>
    <string name="use_cases_threat_sample">Sample Flow: Evidence-like data is saved and instructions left with reliable intermediaries.</string>
    <string name="use_cases_threat_ethics">Ethical Note: The service does not support illegal or harmful activities; compliance with law is mandatory.</string>
    <string name="use_cases_valuable_title">Valuable Deposit Notice</string>
    <string name="use_cases_valuable_desc">Allows elderly individuals to securely pass information about valuables or locations to trusted people.</string>
    <string name="use_cases_valuable_sample">Sample Flow: Information is saved, the ID and password to be shared with family members via a proxy.</string>
    <string name="use_cases_valuable_ethics">Ethical Note: Consent of all parties and legal conformity must be ensured for shared information.</string>
    <string name="why_trust_title">Why Trust Us?</string>
    <string name="why_trust_para1">All source code of this project is open to everyone. You can review it anytime by visiting the GitHub repository.</string>
    <string name="why_trust_para2">Passwords and IDs are never stored on the server. Data is encrypted in your browser and only the encrypted form is sent to the server.</string>
    <string name="why_trust_para3">This keeps your credentials and passwords safe without residing on our systems.</string>
    <string name="tagline_title">⏳🔒 Time-Locked Secure Sharing</string>
    <string name="tagline_sub">Store critical information, wills and investment instructions inaccessibly until the date you choose.</string>
    <string name="settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="select_language">Select language</string>
</resources>
